<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ParallaxScrollView</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_parallax_scroll_view">ParallaxScrollView</string>
    <string name="title_activity_parallax_list_view">ParallaxListView</string>
    <string name="title_activity_simple">SimpleFragmentActivity</string>

    <string name="card_text">A wolf had been badly wounded by dogs. He lay sick and maimed in his lair.He felt very hungry and thirsty. When a sheep passed by, he asked him to fetch some water from the stream."If you bring me the water," he said, "I will find means to get some food.""Yes," said the sheep, "if I bring you the water, you would undoubtedly make me your food." \n\n
One hot summer day a fox was walking through an orchard. He stopped before a bunch of grapes. They were ripe and juicy."I'm just feeling thirsty," he thought. So he backed up a few paces, got a running start, jumped up, but could not reach the grapes.He walked back. One, two, three, he jumped up again, but still, he missed the grapes.The fox tried again and again, but never succeeded. At last he decided to give it up.He walked away with his nose in the air, and said"I am sure they are sour."\n\n
One hot summer day a fox was walking through an orchard. He stopped before a bunch of grapes. They were ripe and juicy."I'm just feeling thirsty," he thought. So he backed up a few paces, got a running start, jumped up, but could not reach the grapes.He walked back. One, two, three, he jumped up again, but still, he missed the grapes.The fox tried again and again, but never succeeded. At last he decided to give it up.He walked away with his nose in the air, and said"I am sure they are sour."\n\n
One hot summer day a fox was walking through an orchard. He stopped before a bunch of grapes. They were ripe and juicy."I'm just feeling thirsty," he thought. So he backed up a few paces, got a running start, jumped up, but could not reach the grapes.He walked back. One, two, three, he jumped up again, but still, he missed the grapes.The fox tried again and again, but never succeeded. At last he decided to give it up.He walked away with his nose in the air, and said"I am sure they are sour."\n\n
A crow felt very thirsty. He looked for water everywhere. Finally, he found a pitcher.But there was not a lot of water in the pitcher. His beak could not reach it. He tried again and again, but still could not touch the water.When he was about to give up, an idea came to him. He took a pebble and dropped it into the pitcher. Then he took another and dropped it in.Gradually, the water rose, and the crow was able to drink the water.\n\n</string>
</resources>
